<Interaction Type="Glossary" ContentFolder="proj_content" Title="Glossary" Numbering="0" animation="bounce" contentfont="Articulate" listwidth="248" jpegquality="80" autoplay="false" autoplayduration="5" headingfont="Articulate" navfont="Articulate" soundeffects="true" volumebutton="true" audioquality="low" audiocustombitrate="br112Kbps" audiocustomfrequency="fq12KHz" audiocustomchannel="ccMono" navbuttons="true" forceorder="false" detectflashver="true" version="2.3.1103.112" borderstyle="round_inset">
  <Filter enabled="true" resulttext="Showing: " headertext="Select a term:" clearbtn="Clear Results" />
  <steps>
    <Step id="285ff8ad-89a0-428a-9c4b-d521823b0b7f" name="Introduction" title="" number="0" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Use this interactive glossary to look up terms and definitions.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;" intro="true">
    </Step>
    <Step id="c03533ff-670b-4f0b-a5b6-9bf2ebe054c2" name="Account" title="" number="30" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;A unique 5 digit number that has been assigned to specific revenue and expense items. Account codes are grouped based on what they are, for example codes that start with 1 are assets such as equipment purchases, codes that start with 4 are revenue, codes that start with 5 relate to payroll and benefits, and codes that start with 6 are other expenditures.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;When a Project is set up by Research Accounting, they also load account codes that can be charged against the Project. For a complete list of account codes please refer to the Financial Services website: &lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color='#0000ff'&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;a target='_blank' href='http://www.pec.ucalgary.ca/financial/reference/businessadminsys_chart'&gt;http://www.pec.ucalgary.ca/financial/reference/businessadminsys_chart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="745f87d4-f753-4278-80e7-d368e0c061c7" name="Account Code" title="" number="31" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;A unique 5 digit number that has been assigned to specific revenue and expense items. Account codes are grouped based on what they are, for example codes that start with 1 are assets such as equipment purchases, codes that start with 4 are revenue, codes that start with 5 relate to payroll and benefits, and codes that start with 6 are other expenditures.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;When a Project is set up by Research Accounting, they also load account codes that can be charged against the Project. For a complete list of account codes please refer to the Financial Services website: &lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color='#0000ff'&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;a target='_blank' href='http://www.pec.ucalgary.ca/financial/reference/businessadminsys_chart'&gt;http://www.pec.ucalgary.ca/financial/reference/businessadminsys_chart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="3217655b-dfab-41e0-870c-5b84ea5310d6" name="Account Description" title="" number="32" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Description of the unique 5 digit account code.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="bcabdee3-3689-465a-afda-8fd7396ce959" name="Activity" title="" number="2" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Five digit field that allows a project to be broken down further. Every project is set up with a ‘00000’ activity code for General, and is how the majority of projects are set up.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="3c798825-f5e9-4b10-9457-fbbabf782a6a" name="Actual" title="" number="7" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Total amount by category charged against the Project for the time period selected.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="1e9422a8-8618-4b5d-8ef5-413fc942d6b6" name="Administrator" title="" number="8" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Name, contact information and location of Research Accounting Administrator assigned to the Project. Note: information listed may not be current.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="9cece7d8-5298-4fab-ab61-49f4955a8032" name="Agency Reporting" title="" number="9" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;This section details the frequency of financial reporting required and specifies the format of the reporting.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="076dcd9e-4045-40b6-8cbd-d5c657957b63" name="Balance" title="" number="3" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;The Project’s life-to-date financial balance at the time the data was last refreshed. It is the sum of actual and encumbered amounts. Under-spent projects are coloured green and show a number in brackets ( ); Over-spent projects are coloured red and reflect a positive number; projects with net spending of zero are not coloured.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="f4f6350e-680b-479b-9e0a-82ba265bb11e" name="Balance Forward for Period" title="" number="10" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Project financial balance prior to time period selected or defaulted (default period is the time period that shows up initially which starts from April to the month the project was selected from the Project List for the University’s current fiscal year). If project started January but selected time period selected for financial information was June to December, the balance forward will reflect the project balance up to May 31st - prior to requested June selected date.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="b0473817-a234-4bba-8144-a02e6baf2ee4" name="Billing" title="" number="11" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;If Billing the Funder is required in order to obtain money, this section lists the currency, frequency and type of invoice format required.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="384c9ea4-9a52-41eb-8f62-2977848a5179" name="Certifications" title="" number="12" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Lists whether Certifications are required for Human, Animal and Biohazards areas. If Certification(s) are required, the Certification Number is listed.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="2aa546b7-abae-481d-b990-7998e46e33b5" name="ChartField" title="" number="42" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Every revenue or expense item that is charged to a Project has to be specifically coded to identify where the amount is to end up. The Accounting String, which is also called the Chartfield, is made up of numbers and letters placed in eight fields.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="5b51feb1-cc75-4721-a1b3-94fd61b556c5" name="Description" title="" number="4" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;This field lists the Project title; the status of the project ie (A) for active, (S) for suspended or (C) for closed; name &amp;amp; UCID of the Project Holder and description of activity code(s).&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="a964c84d-4bb7-40cb-8706-4358f4a88280" name="eFIN" title="" number="1" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;The university’s view only Research Accounting project reporting system.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="5be48245-381a-49d3-8c6c-4d21666a9877" name="Encumbrance" title="" number="13" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Encumbrances reflect amounts that have not yet been spent but for which a financial commitment has been made. Salary encumbrance amounts only show up at the end of the accounting month. This means that salary encumbrances will not be reflected in eFin until the accounting month has officially closed, typically half way through the following month. Currently benefits are not encumbered. Encumbrances are updated daily on Other Expenditures and are based on Purchase Orders that have been placed.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="fc7d06d6-30ec-49ef-9734-83aa484c609a" name="Equipment Ownership" title="" number="14" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Identifies whether equipment purchases are allowed and if so, specifies if ownership remains with the University of Calgary or not. Choices include No Equipment Allowed, U of C - Inventorial Equipment; Not U of C Equipment etc.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="a2a0a871-968a-4a0f-b384-952eceda81c3" name="Fiscal Period" title="" number="33" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Date shown is the calendar year &amp;amp; month when the particular item was charged against the Project and account.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="6a1ad09b-6618-448c-ab98-7cab2b385fa6" name="Journal Line Ref" title="" number="34" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Data appears in this field if the item charged was booked against the Project via a journal entry in People Soft and information was entered in this field (ie PO # etc).&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="3747556e-2e37-4d73-b124-a9d3f2747421" name="Name" title="" number="15" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Name of individual who is a member of the Project Team and what they are authorized to do.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="7dd69fd7-09cf-46a7-a46e-a9e184383645" name="OPR Desc" title="" number="35" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Field populates with name (or UCID) of person or function where entry originated. Entries from HR Payroll do not list anything in this field. Encumbered amounts also do not list anything in this field.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="06e1dd68-4e25-4362-9682-26f1de5ffd15" name="Other Affiliations" title="" number="16" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Section lists other affiliations attached to the Project, if applicable, such as other departments within the University, Other Institutes / Centres or Research Groups.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="fd769b37-60de-412c-b6cc-4a746795aed5" name="Other Expenditures" title="" number="17" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Total of Other Expenditures booked per time period selected. Expenses are always recorded as a debit or positive amount so do not have brackets around them. Account codes charged within this section usually start with a 1 (assets ie equipment), 6 (non-salary expenses) or 7 (internal charges).&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="7aaa029c-fe1c-432b-8c60-7df734f14d61" name="Over-Committed Funds" title="" number="18" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Sum of the columns. A negative amount shown in brackets ( ) indicate the project is under-spent (revenue is greater than spending). A positive amount (no brackets) indicate the project is over-spent (spending is greater than revenue). The amount in the Balance column is colour coded - red for over-spent (stop) and green for under-spent (go).&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="facaece6-cc2a-4059-9fd9-1ebb33de115f" name="Project" title="" number="5" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Unique number (usually starts with RT/PP/OP/IA) that identifies the project. Research Projects start with RT, Institutional Programs Division Projects (IPD, formerly Partnership Programs) start with PP, Operating Projects start with OP, and Internal Projects start with IA.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="a087c692-69bf-4b8f-83bc-0deff793fba0" name="Project Classifications" title="" number="19" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Section lists the category of the Project under General Purpose and the use for the funds under Purpose. Examples of General Purpose categories are Grant, Special Purpose, and Research Salary Award etc. Examples of Use/Purpose of funds are Operating, Travel, Conference, Fellowship &amp;amp; Salary, and Faculty Endowment etc. The Sub-Purpose category identifies if funding is external (Deferred Revenue) or internal (Equity). Awards Status indicates whether the Project is Continuing or a Renewal.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="94cd8f1f-89cf-4312-8c91-d655761af4df" name="Project Effective Dates" title="" number="20" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Lists the beginning and end dates of the Project. Review Date is used for specific Tri-Council Projects and is after the Project End Date. It allows for spending to occur after the End Date but prior to the Review Date. Some fixed price contracts also have Review Dates, which happens if the unused funds are not required to be refunded, then an additional year is given to spend the money out. Final Close Date is entered by Research Accounting when the Project is closed, meaning all applicable reporting has been done (financial and Project Holder), net project is at zero and all advances have been cleared. The Project file is removed from Research Accounting’s active files and placed in storage.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="670b9f8f-317a-41ce-9316-e2669f67143b" name="Project Funding" title="" number="21" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Section details name of the Sponsor/Funder; whether it is a Tri-Council Agency; the Sponsor’s reference number (if applicable) and the classification of the funding.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="2f5d2a12-e076-43d6-ad6b-36786e6cf3ce" name="Project Holder" title="" number="22" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;This section lists the principle investigator of the research project along with their contact information. Also listed is the Fund which identifies the nature and restrictions of the funding. Fund 60 specifies Sponsored Research, and is where the majority of research projects fall. Fund 20 is used for Other Operating Projects while Fund 70 is used for Restricted Projects. Department ID &amp;amp; description where the Project Holder resides is also listed. The fund and Department ID make up part of the accounting chartfield string (along with account number, activity and Project #) which is attached to all transactions charged against a Project. The Status Field is currently not in use. The Pin # listed on the right is for Tri-Council Project use only where a unique number is issued for each Project Holder for CIHR, NSERC &amp;amp; SSERC Projects.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="48b5e7c5-3b34-416c-b163-356e1d84ec17" name="Project Holder Reporting" title="" number="23" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Section lists when progress reports (if applicable) are due from the Project Holder and if this reporting is tied to billing the Sponsor.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="f939792d-1e38-406d-b81c-ffacc3416c77" name="Project Status" title="" number="24" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Indicates if the Project is active, suspended or closed. Active allows revenue and expenses to be booked against the project. Closed means that the project has finished. A project is closed when the research has been completed by the project end date, all required reporting has been done, all advances cleared and the project revenue and expenses net out to zero. Suspended means that the project has been suspended by Research Accounting. This happens when certain requirements have not been met - for example ethics renewal has not happened or when the project has an unauthorized over-expenditure. When a project is suspended, nothing can be booked against it such as payroll, revenue or any other expenditure. Note that in projects that contain more than one activity code, individual activity codes can be closed or suspended even though the overall project remains active.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="3149f44e-edfb-417f-aced-851ba5faefef" name="Project Title" title="" number="25" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Name of the Research Project.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="420b1ad9-e66c-4a42-a3c6-b0ca1a59fa3a" name="Purchase Order" title="" number="36" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Purchase Order Number (PO) assigned by PeopleSoft for items purchased (actual) or to still be purchased (encumbrance) under a PO.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="d93b8b76-0afd-4203-96dc-5cb3b54cfbf5" name="Reference" title="" number="6" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;The Project Sponsor’s unique identification number they have for the Project. Not all Sponsor’s have their own reference number.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="4deaaede-fdf5-4964-be67-72fb539124bb" name="Reference" title="" number="37" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Additional information from PeopleSoft journal entries and AP data if input at source.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="ef68aa3a-3d09-42e1-bfdf-4c1604668f90" name="Reporting Comment" title="" number="38" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Describes what is being charged.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="7afb1066-7649-4549-8728-038d9e8ab871" name="Reporting ID" title="" number="39" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Reporting ID is the UCID for HR Payroll transactions, Invoice Number for AR revenue transactions, PO# for AP transactions, PeopleSoft journal entry number etc.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="81b1db87-4830-4255-8d3b-ed911beecb75" name="Revenue" title="" number="26" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Total of Revenue that has been booked per time period selected. Revenue is always recorded as a credit, or negative value and shows up in &lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color='#0000ff'&gt;&lt;a target='_blank' href='asfunction:GotoStep,a964c84d-4bb7-40cb-8706-4358f4a88280'&gt;eFIN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color='#000000'&gt; with brackets around the number. The account codes charged would have started with a 4.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="e51a1e7a-0889-4599-a895-fe4af636bb33" name="Salary &amp; Benefits" title="" number="27" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Total of Salary &amp;amp; Benefits booked per time period selected. Expenses are always recorded as a debit or positive amount so do not have brackets around them. The account codes charged would have started with a 5. Scholarship and Fellowship payments are not part of this amount as they are not considered employees of the University. They are charged to an account code starting with 63.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="e0715720-c3cc-4717-9b9f-c3c8b8f0fcac" name="Source" title="" number="40" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Indicates where the transaction originated - ie HRP=HR Payroll, RTA=Research Accounting, AP=Accounts Payable, MED=Faculty of Medicine, SYS=System Generated etc.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="4e088342-0121-4b10-bae3-8dd1363479ac" name="Supplier/Customer/Employee" title="" number="41" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Lists name of supplier on PO, name of customer on AR Invoice or name of employee per UCID.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="dfbafea2-e5dc-4c0c-b17e-418ef72b98f4" name="Total Expenditures" title="" number="28" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Sum of Salary &amp;amp; Benefits and Other Expenditures lines within the Financial Summary.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
    <Step id="8e4f9ff4-b15b-4a7f-9a3b-ae71f1d32948" name="Type" title="" number="29" html="&lt;p align='left'&gt;&lt;font face='Articulate' size='13' color=''&gt;Identifies authority given to individual Project Team Member as authorized by Project Holder per Team Authorization Form (TAF) submitted.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;">
    </Step>
  </steps>
  <nextslide enabled="False" text="" show="" />
  <starttip show="false" text="Click next to continue" />
  <resume id="350135f6-5910-4a34-9a14-e0b05fafe12e" enabled="false" />
</Interaction>